各位 不要在走廊奔跑
Ladies, no. No running in the hallway.
搞什么啊
What the fuck?
我们是卡帕会的姐妹 到处都有我们的踪影
Kappa Girls are we! And everywhere we are!
我们戴着神圣的字母K B R
We wear the sacred letters! K, B and R!
现在才早上7点45分 你们在做什么
It's 7:45 in the morning! What is happening?
她惹麻烦了 还是在帮她庆祝
Is she in trouble or are they celebrating her?
我不知道 但以防万一 我还是跟着做
I don't know. I'm just clapping to be safe.
蕾登莫瑞
Leighton Murray, you have been elected
-你获选明年卡帕会的社交主席 -我
- Kappa Social Chair for next year! - Me?
你是否接受姐妹会的 这个重要职位
Do you accept this crucial role in our sisterhood?
我接受
I do!
社交主席可以住 姐妹会宿舍最好的房间
The position comes with one of the absolute best rooms in the house.
我很期待你搬过来
I'm so excited for you to move in.
所以你明年要搬到卡帕会了
So, you're like moving to Kappa next year?
对 我想是吧
Yeah. Yeah, I guess I am.
各位 我们走吧
Let's go, ladies!
我们是卡帕会的姐妹 到处都有我们的踪影
Kappa Girls are we! And everywhere we are!
我们戴着神圣的字母K B R
We wear the sacred letters K, B and R!
我们是卡帕会的姐妹 到处都有我们的踪影
Kappa Girls are we! And everywhere we are...
等等 金柏丽呢
Wait, where's Kimberly?
她们就像离岸流一样把我带走
I just got pulled into their group like a riptide.
各位都知道 学年快结束了
All right, everyone, as you know, the year is nearing its end,
缴交宿舍申请表很快就会截止
and your housing forms are due soon.
没交的人必须参与宿舍抽签
If you don't submit one, you'll have to enter the rooming lottery.
跟没人要的怪胎和败类一起住
And live with the weirdos and losers no one else wants?
-不必了 听起来真惨 -对极了
Oh, no, thank you. That sounds bleak as hell. Truth.
你们清晨时都听到了 我会搬到卡帕会
Well, as you all heard at dawn, I'm moving into Kappa,
我觉得非常幸运
and I am feeling very blessed.
-所以请将我踢出这层楼的信息群组 -好吧
So please do remove me from this floor's text thread. Damn, okay.
还没想清楚的人 我劝你们尽快考虑
And for those of you who haven't figured it out yet, I advise you to think on it.
截止时间很快就到了
The deadline is coming up fast.
佛德拉 我有问题
Frude, related question,
如果有人用廉价胶水 毁了房间的墙壁
if someone sort of destroyed their walls by putting up wallpaper using cheap glue,
会向这个人的父母收费吗
will his or her or their parents be charged for that?
-一定会 -好
Most definitely. Okay.
我还有一个问题 有人有填泥料吗
The second related question, does anyone here have some spackle?
艾赛克斯学生宿舍申请表
我可以问你一件事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
可以啊 什么事
Yeah, for sure. What's up?
-你明年想继续跟我住吗 -天啊 当然
Do you wanna room with me again next year? Oh, my gosh, yes.
我也想问同样的事 但我觉得开口问很羞耻
I was thinking the same thing, but I felt like a total loser for asking.
没错 我完全不想搬去卡帕会宿舍
Totally. I have zero interest in moving into the Kappa house.
我们也已经了解彼此的怪癖了
And I like that we already know each other's quirks.
我有什么怪癖啊
Oh, what are my quirks?
等一下 我不想知道
Wait! Actually, I don't wanna know.
好
Okay.
你有时会在睡梦中跟琼奶奶说话
But sometimes you talk to someone named Grandma Joan in your sleep.
这我听过 营队的人 经常拿这件事说闲话
I've heard that before. People gossiped a lot about it at camp.
我们是要申请三人房 跟贝拉一起住呢
Should we consider a triple and include Bela,
还是我们俩住双人房就好
or doubles and just us?
-两个选项都可以考虑 -当然
- Maybe we consider both? - Sure.
-大家好 -贝拉
- Hey, guys! - Bela.
门关上的时候要敲门
When the door is closed, you knock.
学年要结束了 规则已经不适用了
It's the end of the year. Those rules don't apply anymore.
你们看 我上了杂志 他们把我拍得很好看
Look at this. I'm in a magazine and I look great.
真的耶
You do.
还坐在钢琴边 就像性感版的贝多芬
Sitting at a piano looking like a sexy Beethoven.
我等不及要读了 但我得先去上课
I can't wait to read it, but I got to get to class.
好吧 金柏丽 空出你的时间 我们要把这些发给校园里所有的学生
Fine. But, Kimberly, clear your schedule because we're gonna pass these out to every student on campus.
-你买了几本啊 -75本
How many copies did you grab? Like, 75?
走吧
Come on.
请你读读这个 31和32页有我哦
Hey, read this. I'm featured on pages 31 and 32.
目录也有
Oh, and in the table of contents.
贝拉 这篇文章把你写得好厉害
Bela, you come off amazing in this!
我知道
I know, right?
这可能对我的职涯发展很重要
Dude, this could be, like, huge for my career.
我把内容寄给蒂娜费 在各大电子信箱的地址
I sent it to tina.fey at all the big emails.
我真为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
-你很努力 现在终于有成果了 -谢了
You've been working so hard, and it's finally paying off. Thanks, man.
你和小惠讨论过 明年的住宿了吗
Hey. Have you and Whit talked about housing stuff for next year yet?
还没有 你有什么想法
Oh, no. What were you thinking?
我要和喜剧杂志的 伊凡洁琳和乔搬到校园外
I'm gonna move off-campus with Evangeline and Jo from the comedy magazine.
有道理
Oh, okay. That makes sense.
一定会很棒 我们要一起生活和写作
Yeah, it's gonna be great. We're gonna live together, write together.
甚至一起嗑药
Maybe try drugs together.
就像1970年代的"周六夜现场" 但女性和非白人更多
It's gonna be like SNL from the '70s, but, like, with way more women and non-whites.
-好 当然了 -但我们还是能常见面
- Okay. - We'll still hang out all the time though. - Yeah, for sure.
贝拉 这篇文章太棒了
- Bela! This article rules.
你人真好
That's so sweet.
这是巧嘉 她是《狐狸精》的新写手
This is Jorja. She's one of the newer writers from the Foxy.
我想让你看一些我写的段子 希望你能给我一点想法
Hey, I'd love to send you some pieces I've been working on and get your thoughts on them?
-我很乐意帮忙 -天啊 谢谢你
- I'd be happy to help. Oh, my God, thank you.
太好了 我晚点传信息给你
Amazing. I'll text you later.
太棒了
That was awesome!
你好像校园名人哦
You're like a campus celebrity.
对吧 我算是吧
I know, right? I kinda am.
你比那只我们 喂薯条的胖松鼠有名
You're more famous than that chubby squirrel we feed French fries to.
天啊 我有一阵子没看到它了
Oh, my God. I haven't seen him in a while.
我也是
Me neither.
不会吧
Oh, no.
我无意冒犯
Well, then, with all due respect,
莱西校长是个厌女的大浑蛋
President Lacey is a giant penis who hates all women.
这句话给你引用 贱货
Quote me, bitch.
还是跟平常一样友善
We are making friends like usual, huh?
学校把我们的经费减半
- Essex just cut our funding in half. -
-认真的吗 -我们会撑不下去
- Seriously? - This is gonna kill us.
-等等 他们为何这样 -不知道
- Wait, why would they do that? I don't know.
或许因为异性恋白人生理男 组成的董事会不在乎女性
Maybe because the cis white hetero male board doesn't care about women
或跨性别 或非二元族群
or trans, or non-binary folk.
你坐下吧 帮我们想想办法
Why don't you take a seat, help us figure out what we can do.
不用了
No, I'm good.
我要参加卡帕会的重要活动 顺路来打声招呼
I was just popping in on my way to a very important Kappa event.
从来没人在这栋大楼说过这句话
Oh, something that no one has ever said in this building.
你一定会想到方法的
Well, I am sure you'll find your fix. Okay?
但往后让托娃负责讲电话 他们比你讨喜多了
But, for the future, why don't you just let Tova handle the calls, okay? They are much more likable than you.
我刚也说同样的话
I just said that about myself.
各位 我有好消息
Good news, everyone.
我刚跑了两个捐血站 靠捐血赚到四十美元
Guess who just made us $40 by donating blood at two different locations?
金吉 你还好吗 你脸色很苍白
Ginger, are you okay? You look really pale.
我不能失去这里
I can't lose this place!
好
Okay.
等你忙完 我们可不可以聊聊
Hey, when you're done with that work, can I talk to you for a sec?
我没有在忙 我只是在查 四个人69叫什么
Oh, this isn't work. I'm trying to figure out what it's called when four people 69.
好像叫138
I think it's 138-ing.
这么说有点奇怪
Well, I feel kind of weird for saying this,
但我好像喜欢上同事了
but I think I have feelings for a coworker.
金柏丽 我受宠若惊 但我对你没意思
Kimberly, I am so flattered, but I don't see you that way.
我说的是迦南 我不知道该怎么办
This is about Canaan. I don't know what to do.
我不能跟室友聊 因为他和惠妮交往过
Obviously, I can't talk to my roommates about it because of Whitney and him.
我完全懂你为何会喜欢他
Listen, I totally get why you're into him.
迦南超帅 肌肉大 屁股又翘
Canaan is a hot boy with rippling muscles and two heaping scoops of ass,
但我们都知道 你不能行动
but you and I both know that you can't act on this.
这可能会毁了你的朋友圈 室友关系和职场生涯
It could totally blow up your friend group, your rooming situation, and your work life.
-不值得的 -我知道 但或许他也喜欢我
It ain't worth it. I know, but maybe he has feelings for me too.
-没这回事 -怎么说
- He does not. - How do you know?
我懂他的口味 你不是他的菜
I know his type, and you're not it.
他说你让他想起三年级的老师
He told me you remind him of his third grade teacher.
或许她很不错啊
Maybe she was really cool.
他说她的脚踝超粗
He said she had cankles.
我懂了
- Oh. Got it.
-他说你很像她 -我已经说我懂了
- That would be you in the situation. - Yeah, I said I got it.
我很抱歉 我感觉自己射杀了小鹿斑比
I'm so sorry. I feel like I shot Bambi.
换作是我 我会在学年剩下的时间躲避他
But, if I were you, I would avoid him for the rest of the year
忘了这件事
and forget about it.
你说得对
Yeah, I know you're right.
听着 所有人都有喜欢 但不能追求的人
Listen, we all have crushes that we can't act on.
就像我的可乐送货员
Like me and the Pepsi delivery guy.
虽然我在他的卡车上 放了我胸部的照片
Sure, I left him Polaroids of my tits in his truck,
但我最多只会做到这样 因为我重视这份工作
but that is as far as I'll take it, because I'm a professional.
他听得到啦
I think he can hear you.
我就是要他听到
Yeah, I want him to.
你好 荷黑
Hey, Jorge.
你选好主修科目了
You're declaring your major?
对 我正式成为 生物化学和生物物理系的学生了
Yeah. I'm officially on the biochemistry and biophysics track.
所以你和男友 选一样的主修科目
So, you're gonna do the same major as your boyfriend?
他不是我男友
He is not my boyfriend.
但我觉得自己是他女友 糟透了
But I do think I'm his girlfriend. It's bad.
惠妮 你并不喜欢他 你得赶快斩断情丝
Whitney! You don't like him. You need to end this
不然就会跟他一起上三十堂课 最后跟他结婚
before you take 30 more classes with him and end up marrying his ass.
我会处理的
I will handle it.
我今天就会找他谈
I'm going to talk to him today.
很好 你之前 只试着跟他分手两次
Great. You've only tried to break up with him two other times before,
希望这次会成功
so hopefully this one will stick.
大家好吗
How's everyone doing?
贝拉 搞什么 这篇文章只写到你
What the hell, Bela? This article is entirely about you.
你的名字出现的次数 比我们的杂志还要多
It literally says your name more than the name of our magazine.
怎么会有这种事
How did this happen?
我很抱歉 我也不知道
I'm so sorry. I have no idea.
我以为他要写的是我们所有人
I would have assumed he would have written about all of us.
-有可能是记者喜欢上我了 -不是 他有对象了
Maybe the reporter has a crush on me or something. Nice try. He's seeing someone,
他狠心拒绝我之后告诉我的
which he told me after he rejected me brutally.
这样我就没有头绪了 太奇怪了吧
Then I have no idea how this happened. This is so strange.
上面写的好像《狐狸精》 是你一手打造出来的
It makes it look like you created the Foxy all by yourself.
他在刊登之前让你看过吗
Did he show this to you before he printed it?
没有 如果有的话 我会请他把我的胸部修大一点
No. If he had, I would have asked him to photoshop my boobs to look bigger.
这样吧 我现在打给他 要他撤掉这篇文章
You know what? I'll reach out to him right now and make sure he prints a retraction.
没关系 就当没这回事吧
It's fine. Let's just forget it.
我办不到 我决定了
I don't think I can. In fact,
我不会邀请你来我的准生日派对
you're uninvited to my half birthday party.
要来的人 我订了克莱尔餐厅
For those of you who are coming, I'm registered at Claire's,
希望在场至少有一个人尽快回复
and I would like it if at least one of you RSVP'd.
现在就能直接讲了
You can right now,
不要‥
vocally.
继续工作吧
Let's just get back to work.
她来了 "骄傲的同志爸爸"
There she is.
-女儿 -爸爸
- Hi, honey. - Hi, Dad.
我们讨论一下这件上衣好吗
Hey, can we talk about the shirt?
-好 我想告诉全世界我支持你 -那很好
Yes. I just wanted to show the world how much I support you. That's great.
只是大家可能以为 你是骄傲的"同志爸爸"
It just makes it seem like you're proud to be a gay dad.
我就是啊 我只是‥
Because I am. And I just want...
难怪那个咖啡师语气怪怪的
Oh! That's why the barista called me Zaddy. Yes.
-亲爱的 -妈妈
- Oh, sweetheart. - Hi.
-你好美 -谢谢
- Oh, you look great. - Thanks.
你爸告诉我了
And your father told me.
我是女同志的事 对
That I'm lesbian. Yes, I am.
我只是希望 你能放宽心亲自告诉我
I just wish you felt comfortable telling me yourself.
你不是个好沟通的人
You are not exactly the chillest.
我记得有次度假时 我说想穿球鞋 你就哭了
I seem to remember you crying when I asked to wear sneakers on vacation.
我们去的是圣巴特
It was St. Barts.
我们可能会遇到洛恩麦可斯
We could have run into Lorne Michaels.
为了想该对你说什么 我读了些文章
Well, I read several articles about what to say to you,
我尊重你的性向 而且‥
so I acknowledge your sexuality and
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你准备好要参加 卡帕会春天节了吗
So, are you excited to go to the Kappa Spring Festival?
亲爱的 自从你入会 我就期待着跟你一起参加
Oh, honey. I have been looking forward to going to this event with you since the moment you got in,
我等不及看到 哪些同学变老变丑了
and I cannot wait to see which of my classmates have aged poorly.
祝你们玩得愉快
Well, you girls have fun.
我要去销毁我在1992年写的 伤人社论的唯一副本
I'm off to destroy the only copy of a very hurtful op-ed I wrote in 1992.
-你在做什么 -我在挖一袋咖啡豆
What are you doing? I'm sifting through a bag of beans.
莉拉觉得她的蓝牙耳机在里面
Lila thinks she dropped an AirPod in here.
你的衣服怎么了
What happened to your shirt?
我绊倒了 把燕麦奶洒了一身
I tripped and spilled a gallon of oat milk on myself.
你今晚会去西塔会的派对吗
Oh! Oh, will I be seeing you at the Theta party tonight?
不会 我应该不会去
No. I don't think I can make it.
真可惜
It's too bad.
如果你改变心意再传信息给我
If you change your mind, text me.
我看起来如何
Okay. How do I look?
-很干燥 -对
- Dry. - Right.
回头见
See ya.
-你在这里啊 -天啊 是你啊
- There she is! - Oh, my God. Hi.
准备好看我精湛的报告了吗
Ready to watch me kill this presentation? Whoop!
准备好了
Yeah. Something up?
有什么事吗
But don't worry about it.
有
Yes.
但先别担心 我不想让你分心 我们下课再聊就好
I don't wanna throw you off. We can just talk after class.
我们现在就聊 你不说我就无法专心做实验
No, let's talk about it now. I'm not gonna be able to focus on my experiment if you don't tell me.
-我觉得我们应该分手 -要命
I think we should break up. Shit.
我没想到你会说这个
Okay. It's not what I thought you were gonna say.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没关系
No, it's cool.
我们两个都太忙了 所以就‥
We're both super busy, so this is, like...
好聚好散 也好
It's mutual. It's good.
-你确定吗 -确定
- Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm fine.
我们走吧‥以朋友的身份
Let's get in there as friends. Come on.
我会持续滴定溶液 直到出现沉淀物
So, I'll keep titrating the solution until some precipitate forms,
根据我的估计应该‥
which, according to my estimate, should...
应该‥
Should...
抱歉 我一时分心了
Sorry. Lost my focus.
-老兄 你在哭吗 -没有
Dude, are you crying? No.
只是我的眼睛现在很潮湿
My eyes are just really humid right now.
总之 仔细看烧杯的底部就会发现‥
Anyway, so if you'll focus on the bottom of the beaker, you'll see...
对 我现在哭了
Okay. Now, yes, I am crying.
我要去走廊上独处一下
I think I need a minute alone in the hallway.
爱许丽 你期待明年 担任卡帕会会长吗
So, Ashlie, are you excited to be Kappa president next year?
天啊 非常期待
Oh, my goodness, yes.
我大四时也当过会长
You know, I was president my senior year
我帮姐妹会争取到有网络的电脑
and I got us a computer with the Internet on it.
是这样没错
Yes, you did.
这故事真酷 妈
Cool story, Mom.
爱许丽 做好心理准备 你会遇到很多事情
You need to buckle up, Ashlie. You are in for a lot.
我是校友会成员 感觉每天都有新的危机
I'm on the alumni board and every day it feels like some new crisis.
卡帕会有危机 像是什么
A Kappa crisis? Like what?
有人在浴室装难看的灯光吗
Did they install unflattering lighting in the bathrooms?
-你们听说雪城分会的事了吗 -没有
- No. Did you hear what happened at the Syracuse chapter? - No.
他们禁用了"姐妹会"这个词
- They banned the word "sisterhood."
为什么
Why would they do that?
他们说这个词不精确 因为某些成员不是女性
Well, they said it's not accurate and that some of their members aren't women.
-什么 -我莫名觉得这是好事
What? I don't know. I actually think that's a good thing,
使用更包容跨性别 和非二元族群的语言
you know, to create more inclusive language for trans and non-binary folk.
我觉得如果不把自己视作女性
Well, I just think if you don't see yourself as a woman,
那就去组成自己的社团 让我们当姐妹会
then form your own group. Let us be sisters.
但他们缺乏校方的支持和资金 要怎么自组社团呢
But how can they form their own clubs with no support or funding from the school, you know?
不要误会 我最好的朋友是同志
Just to be clear, - my best friend is a homosexual.
-雷夫吗 -对
- Ralph? - Yes.
-我很爱雷夫 -他很幽默吧
- Love Ralph. Isn't he funny?
我虽然也是同志
Sure, I'm gay, too,
但这件事在这个对话中 不代表什么 不是吗
but that is actually meaningless in the context of this conversation, isn't it?
小蕾 借一步说话好吗
Leight, can I borrow you for a sec?
我知道这些老校友的观念有点过时
Look, I know these boomer alums aren't the most up to date on things,
但今天的重点是跟她们募款
but today is sort of about getting donation checks from them.
我保证 跟她们争不值得
I promise it's not worth engaging.
如果我们不跟她们争 有谁会跟她们争
Right. But if we don't engage with them, then who is going to?
也许你该去找其他人说话
Maybe you should go talk to somebody else.
佐伊 我不想让你难过
Oh, Zoe, I don't mean to rub it in,
但你没有跟迦南一起去 经济系的宴会真是太可惜了
but you really missed out on not going to that Econ banquet with Canaan.
什么经济系的宴会
What Econ banquet?
迦南得奖的那个宴会
The one where Canaan got that award.
超级好玩 而且食物超好吃
It was so fun, and the food was so good.
我喝了一堆汤 结果发现汤只是开胃菜
I loaded up on soup, and then I realized it was just the appetizer.
我不知道你在说什么
Yeah. I don't know what you're talking about.
真的吗
Really?
他说他先邀请你 你没空才邀请我的
He said he invited you before inviting me, and you were busy.
绝对没有这种事
That definitely did not happen.
我失陪一下
Will you excuse me a moment?
莉拉 你想去今晚的西塔会派对吗
Lila, do you wanna go to that Theta party tonight?
妹子 我本来就会去
Bitch, I've been going to go.
我会穿一件突显我胸形的洋装
And I'm wearing a dress that makes my tits sing.
-谢谢你跟我见面 -当然 我很乐意
Thanks again for meeting up with me. Of course. I'm happy to.
谢谢你在期末考抽空跟我见面 其他时间我都没空
Oh, and thank you for meeting me during your final exam. No other times worked for me.
你太厉害了 我想尽可能向你学习
You're just so impressive. I want to learn as much as I can from you.
我读过你的作品集了
So I read your packet and...
-我觉得你该考虑退出《狐狸精》 -退出
- I think you should consider quitting the Foxy. - Quit?
巧嘉 我觉得你很酷 聪明 又幽默
- Jorja, I think you're cool and smart and funny, and in that way,
所以你让我想到自己
you really remind me of myself.
但不是所有又酷 又聪明 又幽默的人都能成为喜剧写手
But not everyone who is cool and smart and funny has what it takes to be a comedy writer.
是哦
Okay?
我知道你能擅长什么了
Oh, you know what I think you'd be great at?
-广告 -什么
- Advertising. - What?
我敢说你一定能写出 可爱的清洁用品广告
I bet you could write really cute commercials for, like, cleaning products,
或是聪明的优格广告
or, like, a clever yogurt ad.
我对那个没兴趣
I'm not really interested in that.
你真的没办法 针对我的作品给任何回馈吗
Do you seriously not have any feedback for me on anything I wrote?
我能告诉你哪些笑话不好笑
I could tell you all the things that didn't really work in here,
但我觉得这只是在浪费我们的时间
but I just don't think that's a good use of either of our time.
天啊 至少你很诚实
Well, at least you're honest.
当然 你没问题的 巧嘉
Always. You got this, Jorja.
你写笑话不行 但其他方面可以的
I mean, not this, but something else.
你要我帮你丢掉吗
Oh, did you want me to throw this away for you?
谢谢你的捐款 对我们会很有帮助
Thank you so much for these. They're gonna do a lot of good.
卡帕会亲亲
Kappa kisses.
宝贝女儿
Honey,
你还好吗 你整天都好安静
are you okay? You've been quiet all day.
我也不确定
Yeah. I don't know.
我‥
I...
我好像不想继续待在这里了
I don't think I want this anymore.
亲爱的 你怎么了
Oh, sweetie, what is going on?
我想跟你一样加入卡帕会
I wanted to be in Kappa just like you,
但我觉得这里让我很不自在
but I don't feel like me when I'm here.
你可能只是改变了 这也没关系
I think you've just changed, and that's okay.
我很抱歉 我知道 你很希望我加入卡帕会
I'm really sorry. I know how bad that you wanted this for me
我不想让你失望
and I just didn't want to let you down.
不会‥别说了
Oh, no, no, stop.
我只是希望你开心
I just want you to be happy.
你不想参加卡帕会 就不要参加
If you don't wanna be in Kappa, then don't.
人生很短 不需要浪费在 让你不快乐的事物上
Life is too short to waste on things that don't bring you happiness.
所以我们才跟奶奶断绝联络
That's why we don't see Grandma anymore.
-我爱你 妈 -我也爱你 蕾登
I love you, Mom. I love you so much, Leighton.
见到你很高兴 蜜咪
Lovely to see you, Mimi.
我也是 莫娜 卡帕会亲亲
Oh, always a pleasure, Mona. Kappa kisses.
真是个笨八婆 对吧
What a dumb whore. Am I right?
-天啊 -她曾经问我"饼干"要怎么写
Oh, my God. You know, she once asked me how to spell the word "biscuit."
妈 你太坏了
Mom, you are such a bitch.
我们一起念大学的话 一定会是好友
Oh, my God, we would have been good friends in college.
那是肯定的
For sure, we would have been.
大一最后一次在派对前喝酒 干啦
Last pregame of freshman year, let's go!
不敢相信这是在这间房的最后一杯酒 我好想哭哦
I can't believe this is the last shot we'll take in this room. I could cry.
我们今天的打扮 是有史以来最辣的
Guys, can I just say that this is the hottest we've ever looked?
惠妮你那身紫色低胸洋装 看起来就像性感版的恐龙邦尼
I mean, Whitney, that dress. Serving purple and serving tits? You look like a sexy Barney.
谢谢‥
Thank you. Thank you.
我现在单身
Listen, I'm single,
我希望这个学年有个精彩的结尾
and I'm ready to end this year with a bang.
我很高兴能跟你们一起玩
Okay. Well, I am just excited to have fun with my girls.
我也是
Me, too.
我的老天爷啊
Holy shit.
-各位暂停一下 -怎么了
- Guys, stop! - What's wrong?
-我要被取消了 -什么
- I'm getting canceled. - What?
《狐狸精》有个女生 在社群媒体上炮轰我
This girl from the Foxy is blasting my ass on social media.
-我确定没那么糟啦 -对啊
- I'm sure it's not that bad. - Yeah.
我在艾赛克斯所谓的 女性主义喜剧杂志学到五件事
Five things I learned at Essex's so-called feminist comedy magazine.
或许是在赞美你 她说学到东西了
Maybe it's a nice post. She said she learned things.
贝拉摩赫查是个 厌女的喜剧独裁者
"Bela Malhotra is a misogynistic comedy dictator"
她痛恨所有女性 包括她自己
who hates all women, including herself.
太糟糕了
Fuck. This is so bad.
天啊 我得放弃喜剧 跟我的笨蛋亲戚一样去当药师了
Oh, my God. I'm gonna have to quit comedy and become a pharmacist like all my dumb cousins.
一定有什么误会
There has to be a misunderstanding.
我同意 你绝对不讨厌自己
Yeah, I agree. I mean, you definitely don't hate yourself.
-你反而是过度自恋了 -没错
- If anything, you like yourself too much. - Exactly.
听着 你明天去找她把话说清楚
Listen, just talk to this girl tomorrow and smooth it over.
-别让这件事毁了今晚 -我赞同惠妮
- Yeah. - You don't need to let it ruin your night. I'm with Whitney.
那女的只有四十个追踪者 没人会看到她的文章
I mean, the girl has, like, 40 followers, okay? Nobody will ever see that.
你们说得对 出门前再喝一杯吧
Yeah, you're right. All right, let's take one more shot before we go.
-没错 谢谢你 -这就对了
Yes. Thank you.
或者小睡五分钟再出门
Or we could take a five-minute nap and then go.
-你在开玩笑吗 -好啦
- Are you fucking kidding me? - No! All right.
天啊 这个派对太棒了
Shit! This party is going off.
我最爱的贱货们来了 好极啦
My favorite bitches! Yeah!
欢迎来到大冒险派对
Welcome to the Dare or Dare Party.
你们得进行酒杯底下写的大冒险
You are obligated to do the dare written on the bottom of your cup.
-有哪种大冒险 -我都看过了 那边的都是色色的事
Oh! What kind of dares? I've read them all. On the side of the table, they're horny.
这边的简直下流
And here, they're just plain nasty.
我两边都各拿了一杯
I took one of both. Oh.
跟红发的人亲嘴
Smash face with a redhead.
我要那一杯
I want that one.
-好 -谢谢你
- Okay. - Thank you.
该死 乔丝琳 我不要在这里揉陌生人的胸部
Damn it, Jocelyn, I'm not gonna jiggle a stranger's tit at this party.
怎么是"电臀舞" 我办不到 小时候我被禁止用下半身跳舞
Twerk? I can't twerk. I wasn't allowed to dance with my bottom half growing up.
我们不必真的做 对吧
We don't actually have to do these, do we?
乔丝琳显然不这么觉得
Oh, Jocelyn seems to think we do.
天啊
Oh, my God.
好咸湿的吻
That is a lot of tongue.
我今晚把牙齿刷得很干净
I brushed my teeth so good tonight,
一定能在派对上找到人亲热
I am 1,000% making out with someone at this party.
我们组成搭档 帮助彼此向帅哥美女进攻吧
Let's pick out some hotties and wingwoman each other hard.
好啊‥
Okay. Okay,
我来物色一下对象
sure. Let's see my options.
有个男的在吸塔可钟的辣酱包
Okay. We got a guy slurping a Taco Bell fire sauce packet.
还有一个舞步 根本赶不上拍子的人
And a dude who's dancing tragically off the beat.
现场没有我喜欢的类型
Yeah. I don't think any of these guys are my type.
你要找的是什么类型
So, what are you looking for?
找到我再告诉你
I will let you know when I see it.
-你来了 -是你
- Hey. - Hey!
-你不是说没办法来吗 -结果我还是来了
I thought you said you weren't coming? Turns out I am, and did.
-你在做什么 -找到我想做的大冒险酒杯
What are you doing? I'm trying to find a cup with a dare I actually wanna do.
这杯写着"脸埋进莉拉胸部" 上面还有她的号码
This one says, "Motorboat Lila," and it has her phone number.
一定是她自己写的
Yeah, she definitely wrote that one.
做个举手之劳 把那杯丢掉好吗
Can you just be a good citizen and throw it out?
那杯上面写什么
Wait, what's that one?
亲吻陌生人
Kiss a stranger.
这个还不错
That one's not a bad one.
我们认识彼此 所以你安全了
Well, we both know each other, so you're in the clear, sir.
是啊
Yeah.
迦南
- Yo, Canaan! - Oh!
我朋友到了 我要‥
My friends just got here, so I'm gonna...
-行 你去吧 -好 先走了 再见
Yeah, of course. Go. - I'll go. All right. - Yeah.
金吉 我喜欢你在室内穿大衣
Ginger, love that you're wearing a long coat indoors.
谢谢 这件是我的老人邻居的
Thank you! It belonged to my elderly neighbor.
我不能久待
But I can't stay long.
我今晚又捐了两次血 现在很虚弱
I gave blood twice again this evening, so I am feeling weak.
而且我不喜欢 那个男的看我的眼神
Also, I do not like the way that guy is looking at me.
-你去找地方坐吧 -好
- Why don't you go sit down? - Okay.
-我晚点再去照顾她 她没事的 -确定她没事
- I'll go deal with that later. - You sure she's good? - She's fine.
卡帕会怎么样
So, how is Kappa?
-我退出了 -不会吧
I quit. Oh, no.
你找到有更多 金发女的地方住了吗
Did you find an even blonder place to live?
-等等 你是说真的 -是真的
Wait, are you being serious? I am.
我发现我宁愿 在女性中心多花点时间
I decided I would rather spend my time at the Women's Center,
跟我真正喜欢的人相处
you know, with people I actually like.
如果你又破坏雕像被罚社区服务
If this is because you vandalized another statue and got community service,
我会发现的
I will find out.
对了 还有这个
Also, I have this.
天啊 三万美元
Holy shit! $30,000?
我妈本来要捐给卡帕会
My mom was gonna donate it to Kappa,
我告诉她哪里更用得上这笔钱
so I told her where it would do better things.
这笔钱能救我们一命
This is going to completely save us!
-抱歉 我不该这么做的 -没关系‥你应该要的
I am so sorry. I should not have done that. No, no, no, no, no. You should have.
你女友泰坦怎么办
What about your girl Tatum?
在你募款会那天晚上 我跟她分手了
I ended things with her. The night of your fundraiser, actually.
因为我打扮成艾尔顿强很性感吗
Because of how hot I looked in my Elton John costume?
那套衣服还在 我现在可以马上去换
You know, I still have that. I could go get it right now.
够了啦
Shut up.
迦南 你要走了
Canaan, are you leaving?
对 我们要去埃奇伍德的派对
Yeah. A bunch of us are headed to a party on Edgewood.
你想一起来吗
You wanna come with?
不用了 我要留在这里
Oh! No. I'm going to stay.
-祝你玩得开心 -好 再见
Have fun.
-贝拉 -是你们啊
Okay, bye. - Bela. - Hey!
这里有一张沙发要丢 我们搬到明年的宿舍好吗
There's a couch here that they're trying to get rid of. Should we take it for the house next year?
他们叫那张沙发"精子银行" 但我们不必沿用
They call it the sperm bank, but we don't have to call it that.
-巧嘉的贴文太夸张了 -我知道
That post from Jorja is so messed up. I know.
她反应太大了 对吧
Huge overreaction, right?
喜剧写手要脸皮厚一点 看看我在《卡特兰》的遭遇
Copywriters need to have a thick skin. Look at all the stuff that happened to me at the Catullan.
我们不是站在你这边的
Dude, we're not agreeing with you.
你在《卡特兰》的遭遇确实很糟
What happened to you at the Catullan was horrible.
我们开办这本杂志 就是为了提供一个友善的环境
And our magazine was created to be a better alternative to that toxic shit.
你不记得了吗 这个团队是你建立起来的
Don't you remember? I mean, since you were the one who created our group.
等等 你们是在气这件事吗
Wait, is that what this is about?
你们只是在气 我在那篇文章中得到太多功劳
You guys are just mad that I'm still getting too much credit in that article.
我们跟那个记者谈过了 贝拉
We talked to the reporter, Bela.
他先让你看过文章 你骗了我们
He showed you the article. You lied to us.
那篇文章是一回事 贝拉自私是很正常的
That article was one thing. That was normal, selfish Bela.
但对巧嘉那么狠毒是不对的
But being that brutal to Jorja, it's not okay.
巧嘉在网络上对你的描述
And what Jorja put online about you?
我觉得非常恰当
I'd say it was pretty fucking well-written.
-你被逐出《狐狸精》了 -什么
- You're fired from the Foxy. - What?
显然只有你符合你的喜剧水平
Clearly, you're the only person who lives up to your own comedy standards,
你就自己一个人搞笑吧
so go be funny alone.
拜托别这样 这样我们明年当室友会很尴尬
No, please don't do this. This is gonna make living together super awkward next year.
我们把你的房间让给卡拉了
- We gave your room to Carla.
-等等 真的吗 -真的
- Wait, we did? - We did.
-也好 -等一下‥
Fine.
该死
Fuck!
莉拉 我可以问个问题吗
Hey, Lila, can I ask you a question?
我目前不接受回答问题
I'm not currently taking any questions.
杯子说我得找五十个人接吻
My cup said I had to find 50 people to kiss
但我只找到34个
and I've only found 34.
-好 35个了 -很高兴能帮忙 你看到迦南了吗
- Oh. - Okay, 35. Happy to help. Have you seen Canaan?
-他刚才离开了 -好吧
- He left a little bit ago. - Okay.
若你见到他 请他明天要开啜饮馆的门
But if you see him, let him know that he's gonna open up Sips tomorrow
因为我打算请病假
because I do plan on calling out sick to myself.
好
- Okay.
再见 35号
- Bye, 35.
你好 36号
Hi, number 36.
你好可爱 你喜欢比 自己高很多的女生吗
You're cute. You like your women much, much taller than you?
迦南
Canaan!
我可以跟你说句话吗
- Hey. - Hey. Can I talk to you for a sec?
好啊
Yeah.
你们先走吧 我等等过去
Y'all go on. I'll catch up with you.
-怎么了 -你骗了我
- What's up? - You lied.
我骗你
I lied?
-骗你什么 -佐伊
About what? Zoe.
你没邀请她参加活动
You never invited her to that event.
她跟我说了 你为什么要说谎
She told me. Why would you lie?
好问题
That's a great question.
因为我根本没理由骗你
Because that lie would make no sense.
你希望我跟你一起去 我是你第一个邀请的人
You wanted me to go with you. You invited me first.
好吧 你说得对
Fine, I did.
你想让我难堪吗
You trying to embarrass me or something?
我有消息要宣布
So, I have some news.
我跟艾丽西亚复合了
Alicia and I are back together.
说实话 我很开心
And, I'm not gonna lie, I am really happy about it.
好耶
Yay!
等等 如果你不搬去卡帕会 贝拉也不搬到校外
Wait, so if you're not moving into Kappa and Bela's not living off-campus anymore,
我们明年还是能一起住
then we can all live together next year.
如果你们愿意的话
I mean, if you all want.
-我愿意 -你呢 贝拉
- You know what, I'm down. - What about you, Bela?
我‥
Yeah.
抱歉 我今早还是有点分神
Sorry. I'm just a little distracted this morning.
你还在想杂志社 那个女生的事吗
Is this still about that girl from the magazine?
何不找她谈谈呢
Why don't you just talk to her, right?
她一定愿意听你说的
I'm sure she would be open to hearing you out.
当然 我十点十五分要找人谈谈
Yeah. Totally, I have a meeting about it at 10:15.
-很好啊 -太好了 这样就好
Great. Okay, good, I'm glad.
金柏丽 你昨晚过得如何
So, Kimberly, how was your night?
有什么有趣的事吗
Anything interesting happen?
没有发生什么事
No, not really.
可以尝到桃子的味道
You really taste the peach in this one.
听说蕾登放弃了明年的房间
- Hey! - Hey. So, I heard Leighton turned down that room for next year?
-对 -我想要那个房间
Yeah. I want it.
好 坐吧
Okay. Take a seat.
我很无礼 不尊重她
I was rude and disrespectful
我觉得自己很糟糕
and I feel awful about it.
我为了《卡特兰》来到艾赛克斯
I came to Essex for the Catullan.
结果搞砸了
That blew up.
而且我‥
I got
还被新的杂志社开除
kicked out of this new group.
没人想跟我合作
No one wants to work with me.
我的学业成绩平均积点 只有一点八
I have a 1.8 GPA.
我因为自私伤透了一个好人的心
I broke an amazing guy's heart by being selfish.
我只希望大家喜欢我
All I want is for people to like me,
但我不断伤害他们
but I just keep hurting people instead...
所以我想转学
So I'd like to transfer.
本季终
谢谢观赏